Guide to the United Ministries in Higher Education Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Publications, 1955-1996; Series IV
  - Other articles and essays
    - Drake, G. Bryant. "Our Campus Mission", Advance, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Dynes, Russell R. and E. L. Quarantelli. "Disruption on the Campuses of Ohio and the Universities", Spring, 1970. A Report prepared for the Ohio Council of Churches and the Ohio Board United Ministries in Higher Education. (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Faith, Science and Technology Forum. Paper published by Education in Society, National Council of Churches of Christ, USA. I, II, III, IV., 1983 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Gibb, Jack R. "Dynamics of Leadership", 1967 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Gibson, Samuel N. "Viewpoints on Higher Education: The Report of a Study of the Attitudes of Pennsylvanians Towards Higher Education", 1973 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Gould, Samuel B. "Leadership in a Time of Educational Change", 1969 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Green, Alan W.C. "Financing Campus Ministry: An Overview", (Newton Centre, MA: Insitute for Campus Ministries), n.d. (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Grogan, Wells. "The Mission of the Church in Relation to the University", 1962 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Gustafson, James M. "Foundations of Ministry" (Box 44, Folder 471)
    - Hammond, Phillip E. "The Campus Clergyman", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Harrison, Jack. "Dwelling with Man", 1967 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Helmich, Hartland H. "The Mission of the Church in the University", 1966. (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Higher Education Committee, Redwoods Presbytery. "The Need to Reorder the Church's Ministry to the Campus", 1992 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Hilberry, Conrad. "Growing New Leaders", 1968 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Holt, Roy D. "The Church and Campus: What is the Church's Mission on Campus?", 1965 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Hough, Joseph C. Jr. "The University as the City of Human Hope", Occasional Papers, United Methodist Board of Higher Education and Ministry, 1:16 (Dec 14, 1977). (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Huber, Robert T. "The Campus Ministry in Our Time", 1963 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Huber, Robert T. "Elements Involved in Developing a Strategy in Higher Education", 1967 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Hughes, Everett C. "Are the Clergy a Profession?", n.d. (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Johnson, Lewis. "The Changing Role of the Campus Ministry", 1962 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Jones, Lawrence N. "Why is the Church on the Modern College Campus?" United Church Herald, November 26, 1959. (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Juergensmeyer, Mark. "Live Campus, Dead Church", 1968 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Kinnamon, Michael. "The Church and Higher Education", 1992 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Laurie, William K. "The Proper Work of the University", 1965 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Leavitt, Harold. "Entrepreneurs, Mark II", 1967 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Loats, Leroy S. "History, Trends and Developments in Campus Ministry", 1964 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - "The Local Church and Higher Education: Papers presented at a conference held at Jamestown College-Summer 1965" (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Lovell, William M. "An Ecumenical Ministry in the University", 1972 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    - Marschall, John P. "A Theological Rationale for a Coalition of Local Church and Community college in Joint Mission", 1976 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - McGown, David J. "A Perspective/Speculation on Higher Education Ministry applied to Illinois United Minstries in Higher Education and The Synod of Lincoln Trails", 1990 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - McNeur, Ronald E. "The Ministry in Higher Education", n.d. (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - "The Ministry of the Church in Higher Education", The Duke Divinity School Review, 42:2 (Spring 1977). (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - "Ministry to Postsecondary Education in Florida", Institute for Social Policy Studies, Dec, 1975. (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - Monsonis, James. "Trends in Campus Ministry", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - Montana Association of Churches: Community Based Campus Ministry. "A Seed Catalog for Community Based Campus Ministry", Second Edition, March 1994. (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - Mulley, Earl. "Why Does the Church Minister to the Campus", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - Murry, William. "The Church and the University", 1963 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - The NCMA Papers: "Shaping the Technological Future", 1986 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - New University Thought, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - Newsletter of the Synod of Lincoln Trails, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - n.a., "It was all so different before everything changed", 1980 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - n.a., "A concept of the campus ministry", n.d. (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - New Staff Seminar, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - n.a., "A Proposed definition for the University Ministry", n.d. (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - n.a., "Prelude to the University Ministry", 1967 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - n.a., "The Nature of Ministry in and with Higher Education" (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - "Pedagogy in Higher Education", Dubuque Theological Seminary (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - "Presbyterian 101", Church and Society, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 473)
    - Price, David. "A Strategy for Serious Churchmen", 1966 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Pruyne, Jim, "New Covenant Community", 1994 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Pruyne, Jim. "A Strategy for the Campus Ministry", 1965 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Robinson, Clyde. "Ministries in Higher Education: The Current Ecumenical Scene", 1988 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Robinson, Clyde. "A Response to: The Church's Ministry in Higher Education current strategies: an exploration and education", 1978 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Rogers, William. "The Nature of the Campus Ministry and the challenge to Presbyterians at Cornell University", 1961 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Robert, Newman. "Christianity Preaching from unexpected pulpits", 1960 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Roy, Lucien. "Points of Intersection", n.d. (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Rutledge, Mark. "Parish-Based Ministry in Higher Education: What Makes it Work?", n.d. (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Sanford, Nevitt. "Leadership for Improved Conditions for Learning and Research" (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Schilling, Harold. "An Address at MSU", 1960 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Schwehu, Mark. "Church Related Higher Learning in the Post-Modern World", n.d. (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - SCM Discussion: Campus Ministry through the Student Christian Movement, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Smith, Harry. "Between two-worlds: The Role of the University Christian Worker", 1956 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Smith, Harry. "Congregation and Campus", 1967 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Smith, Seymour. "Religious cooperation in State Universities: An Historical Sketch", 1957 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Smith, Verlyn. "Higher Education Ministry and the local Congregation", 1971 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Steckel, Clyde. "A Sermon for the Campus Ministry", n.d. (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Steckel, Clyde. "The shifting Aims and Purpose of the Campus Ministry" (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Steckel, Clyde. "UCCF Philosophy and Strategy of Ministry", 1967 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - The Study of Religion on the Campus of Today, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 474)
    - Tarcher, Martin. "Leadership: Organization and Structure", 1967 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Thomason, Robert. "Statement of Mission for United College Ministries in North Virginia", 1993 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Trotter, F. Thomas. "A Theological Basis for Higher Education", 1975 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Tuchman, Barbara. "The Missing Element", 1967 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Wallick, David E. "The Role of the Professional 'Campus Pastor' ", 1966 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Wallick, David E. "A Preliminary paper on the campus minister as 'Marginal Man' ", n.d. (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Wallick, David E. "The Role of the Professional 'campus pastor' ", 1966 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Wallick, David E. "Toward an undertanding of the Nature of the Ministry in Higher Education", 1968 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - Williams, George. "The World, the Church and the University", 1963 (Box 45, Folder 475)
    - A Point of View, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 476)
- State Commissions, 1957-1993, n.d.; Series V
  - Alaska, 1968-1977 (Box 46, Folder 478)
  - Arkansas, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 479)
  - California, Northern, 1962-1978 (Box 46, Folder 480)
  - California, Southern, 1974-1992 (Box 46, Folder 481)
  - Colorado, 1973-1986 (Box 46, Folder 482)
  - Connecticut, 1973-1988 (Box 46, Folder 483)
  - Florida, 1966-1975 (Box 46, Folder 484)
  - Hawaii, 1970-1977 (Box 46, Folder 485)
  - Idaho, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 486)
  - Illinois, 1964-1996 (Box 47, Folder 487)
  - Indiana, 1973-1989 (Box 47, Folder 488)
  - Iowa, 1964-1968 (Box 47, Folder 489)
  - Kansas, 1963-1971 (Box 47, Folder 490)
  - Kentucky, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 491)
  - Louisiana, 1966-1972 (Box 48, Folder 492)
  - Maine, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 493)
  - Massachusetts, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 494)
  - Michigan, 1974-1993 (Box 48, Folder 495)
  - Minnesota, 1962-1993 (Box 48, Folder 496)
  - Mississippi, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 497)
  - Missouri, 1962-1972 (Box 48, Folder 498)
  - Montana, 1984-1991 (Box 48, Folder 499)
  - Nebraska, 1963-1982 (Box 48, Folder 500)
  - Nevada, 1974-1988 (Box 48, Folder 501)
  - New England, 1962-1973 (Box 49, Folder 502)
  - New Jersey, 1961-1986 (Box 49, Folder 503)
  - New Mexico, 1972-1987 (Box 49, Folder 504)
  - New York, 1957-1988 (Box 49, Folder 505)
  - North Carolina, 1965-1975 (Box 49, Folder 506)
  - North Dakota, 1962-1972 (Box 50, Folder 507)
  - Ohio, 1962-1995 (Box 50, Folder 508-509)
  - Oklahoma, 1964-1987 (Box 50, Folder 510)
  - Oregon, 1969-1987 (Box 50, Folder 511)
  - Pennsylvania, 1963-1984 (Box 51, Folder 512-514)
  - Puerto Rico, 1964-1966 (Box 51, Folder 515)
  - Rhode Island, 1975-1977 (Box 51, Folder 516)
  - South Dakota, 1963-1993 (Box 51, Folder 517)
  - Texas, 1968-1993 (Box 51, Folder 518)
  - Utah, 1971-1974 (Box 51, Folder 519)
  - Vermont, 1963-1975 (Box 51, Folder 520)
  - Virginia, 1974-1992 (Box 51, Folder 521)
  - Washington, 1968-1977 (Box 52, Folder 522)
  - Wisconsin, 1960-1990 (Box 52, Folder 523)
  - Wyoming, 1970-1984 (Box 52, Folder 524)
- Financial Records, 1979-1986; Series VI
  - 1979
    - Ledger, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 213)
    - Payroll Record, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 214)
    - Check Register, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 215)
    - Audit Confirmations, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 216)
    - Budget, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 217)
    - Bank Deposits, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 218)
    - Bank Statements, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - Campus Ministry Boards, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 220)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 221)
    - Ministries in Public Education, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 222)
  - 1980
    - Ledger, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 223)
    - Payroll Record, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 224)
    - Check Register, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 225)
    - Audit Confirmations, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Budget, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - Bank Statements, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Bank Deposits, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Campus Ministry Boards, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Interdenominational Work, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Career Development, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 233)
  - 1981
    - Ledger, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Audit, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Treasurer's Report, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 236)
    - Check Register, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 237)
    - Payroll Sheets, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 238)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 239)
    - Bank Deposits, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 240)
    - Bank Statements, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 241)
    - Campus Ministry Boards, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 242)
    - Interest, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 243)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 244)
    - Public Education, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 245)
    - Career Development, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 246)
  - 1982
    - Ledger (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - Audit, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - Financial Records, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - Bank Statements, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - Deposit Forms, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - Cash Receipts, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - Philadephia Savings Account, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - Career Development, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 254)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - Philadephia Wage Tax, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 257)
    - California Wage Tax, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 258)
    - Federal Taxes, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 259)
    - Pennsylvania Payroll Tax, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 260)
    - Copies of Checks Sent, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 261)
    - Former Employee Records, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 262)
  - 1983
    - Ledger, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 263)
    - Audit, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - Budget, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 265)
    - Financial Reports, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 266)
    - Bank Statements, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 267)
    - Cash Receipts, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 268-271)
    - Payroll Records, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 272)
    - Mary Abbott, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 273)
    - Frances E. Bolles, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 274)
    - Gary A. Bolles, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 275)
    - Joy DeLara, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 276)
    - Frank M. Harron, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 277)
    - Nancy Minout, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 278)
    - Samuel Totten, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 279)
    - Harold Viehman, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 280)
    - Lewis L. Wilkens, Jr., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 281)
    - Annuity fund dues and insurance, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 282)
    - Career Development, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 283)
  - 1984
    - Ledger, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - Audit, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 285)
    - Budget, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 286)
    - Treasurer's Report, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 287)
    - Bank Statements, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    - Cash Receipts, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 289)
    - Journal Transfers, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 293)
    - Betsy A. Tureky, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 294)
    - Career Development, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 295)
  - 1985
    - Ledger, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 296)
    - Audit, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 297)
    - Financial Report, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 298)
    - Bank Statements, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 299)
    - Cash Receipts, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 300-302)
    - Journal Transfers, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 303)
    - Career Development Accounting, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 304)
  - 1986
    - Ledger, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 305)
    - Audit, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 306)
    - Treasurer's Report, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 307)
    - Bank Statements, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 308)
    - Cash Receipts, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 309-310)
    - Journal Transfers, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 311)
    - Career Development Accounting, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 312)
    - Check Register - bound volume, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 313)
    - Task Force on UME's Financial Life, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 555)
  - Tax and Miscellaneous Records
    - Application for exempt status-Pennsylvania, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - IRS Form 1096 1095, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - W2 and W3, 1974-1981 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Personal Income Tax- Pennsylvania, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Income and Social Security Taxes, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 203)
    - Wage tax-Missouri and Kansas City, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 204)
    - NY City and State Personal Income Tax, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Rental Allowance Forms, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 206)
    - Correspondence with IRSand legal counsel, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 207)
    - IRS Forms 941, 1975-1982 (Box 13, Folder 208)
    - Wage-tax Philadephia, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 209)
    - Form 990, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 210)
    - Pennsylvania Unemployment Insurance, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 211)
    - California Income Tax, 1976-1982 (Box 14, Folder 212)
    - Taxes-Federal withholding and Social Security, pre-1987 (Box 25, Folder 314)
    - Taxes-CA withholding and disability insurance (Box 25, Folder 315)
    - Taxes-Pennsylvania, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 316)
    - Taxes-North Carolina, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 317)
    - Irene Jennings, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 318)
    - Carol Kelly, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 319)
    - Betty Reardon, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 320)
    - Suzette D. Rodriquez, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 321)
    - Joy DeLara, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 322)
    - Sarah C. Nelson, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 323)
    - Better business bureau, n.d (Box 25, Folder 324)
    - Boatman's West Port Bank, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 325)
    - Provident National Bank, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 326)
    - Insurance, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 327)
    - Grace E. Colson, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 328)
    - Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1971, 1975-76 (Box 26, Folder 329)
    - By-laws, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 330)
    - Mailing List, 1942-1984 (Box 26, Folder 331)
    - Annual Financial Statements, 1975-1982 (Box 57, Folder 553)
    - Annual Financial Statements, 1983-199352 (Box 57, Folder 554)
- Related Organizations and Material, 1944-1995, n.d; Series VII
  - American Baptist Church, 1979-1982 (Box 52, Folder 525)
  - Anglican (Church of England), 1982 (Box 52, Folder 526)
  - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), 1987 (Box 52, Folder 527)
  - Christian Faith and Higher Education Institute, 1964-1969 (Box 52, Folder 528)
  - Church Society For College Work, 1967-1975 (Box 52, Folder 529)
  - Collected Resources, 1990s (Box 53, Folder 530)
  - Denominational Executives, 1977-1987 (Box 53, Folder 531)
  - Denominational Material, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 532)
  - Episcopal Church, 1976-1982 (Box 53, Folder 533)
  - Faculty Christian Fellowship, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 534)
  - Lutheran Church, 1969-1991 (Box 53, Folder 535)
  - Methodist Church/United Methodist Church, 1957-1977 (Box 53, Folder 536)
  - Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 537)
  - Ministries in Public Education, 1969-1979 (Box 54, Folder 538)
  - National Council of Churches, 1961-1975 (Box 54, Folder 539-540)
  - National Ecumenical Student Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 541)
  - National Ecumenical Student Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 542)
  - National Ecumenical Student Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 543)
  - National Student Christian Federation, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 543A)
  - Peacemaking, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 397)
  - Presbyterian Church USA, 1955-1984 (Box 55, Folder 544)
  - Presbyterian Church USA and UCC, 1955-1958 (Box 55, Folder 545)
  - Student Christian Movement: Study Books, 1956-1962 (Box 56, Folder 546)
  - Roman Catholic Church, 1976-1988 (Box 56, Folder 547)
  - UME-ESPC, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 548)
  - United Campus Christian Fellowship, 1959-1964 (Box 56, Folder 549)
  - United Church of Christ, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 550)
  - United Presbyterian Church in the USA, 1959-1981 (Box 57, Folder 551)
  - United Student Christian Council, 1950-1956 (Box 57, Folder 551A)
  - United Student Fellowship, 1944-1958 (Box 57, Folder 552)
  - University Christian Movement, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 552A)
- Christian Faith and Higher Education Institute, 1962-1971; Series VIII
  Scope and Contents
  The Christian Faith and Higher Education Institute, a program of UMHE, operated from 1962 through 1971.
  - Study and Strategy Committee
    Chronological files of the committee consist of meeting minutes and documents considered at the meetings
    - Documents re. establishment of a Christian Faith and Higher Education Study Center at Michigan State University, East Lansing, 1959-1962 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Documents and minutes from meeting of 1962 Jun 7-8 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, consultation report, conference program, 1962 Oct - 1963 Feb (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, brochure, conference program, 1963 Mar-Sep (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, report to Projects Committee, publications and reports, including "Theology and Natural Science" by Robert Tobias, "Resources of the Christian Faith for the Scientist" by Burton J. Moyer, "Faith, Learning and Commitment" by L. J. Tolle, Jr., "Pedagogy in Higher Education" ed. by Davide E. Engel, "A Model of the Moral Actor in Contemporary Society" by Kenneth Underwood, 1964 Mar (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, brochure, report, proceedings of conference on "The Work of the University in the United States", report of "Consultation on the Church's Ministry in Higher Education", 1964 Sep-Dec (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, report to Projects Committee, publication: "Freedom and Responsibility in Higher Education" by Herbert H. Stroup, 1965 Mar (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Brochure, minutes, publications and reports, including "A Church and a College" by John R. Fry, "Reflections on Pacem in Terris", "Ethical Problems in Organ Transplantation" by John C. Holden, 1965 Sep (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, publications and reports including "Some Preliminary Findings on Summer Civil Rights Volunteers, 1965", "Exploring Higher Education 1962-1965", "The End of Intimacy" by Arthur C. McGill, 1966 Mar (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, reports, 1966 Sep (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, brochure, 1967 Mar (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, reports and publications including "Overlive" by William M. Birenbau, "Issues of Freedom and Autonomy in American Higher Education" by H. Lynn Jondahl, "Exploration in Undergraduate Education" discussion summary, 1967 Sep (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, reports and publications including re. "Conference on the Delivery of Health Services", 1968 Apr (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, corespondence, publication "Internationalization of the Curriculum in Higher Education: A Bibliography" by Arthur F. Grisham, 1969 Feb (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, memos, publications, including "Higher Education Under Pressure", 1969 Dec (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, memos, documents related to "Conversations About Higher Education" event, 1970 Apr (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, report re. Institute, issue of Motive related to "Crisis of the Environment", 1970 Nov (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Memo, minutes, budget, 1971 Jan (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Termination of Institute, 1971 Jun-Nov (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Other publications and papers of Institute, including "The University in Triple Jeopardy" by William B. Boyd, "Policy Development Task Force Report, "Toward a Concept of Education as Advocacy", 1970, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - National Administration and Policy Committee, Christian Faith and Higher Education Projects
    This Committee became known as the National Committee for Christian Faith and Higher Education Projects. Chronological files of the committee consist of meeting minutes and documents considered at the meetings.
    - Minutes, background documents, "Working Principles and Articles of Operation", 1963 Jan (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, "Working Principles and Articles of Operation", report from Provisional Regional Study and Strategy Committee North Central Region", proposal for development of Christian Faith and Higher Education Study Center, 1963 May (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, correspondence, reports, 1964 Feb (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, correspondence, reports, 1964 Oct (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Report to Project Committee from Christian Faith and Higher Education Institute, East Lansing, 1965 Mar (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - [Now called National Committee for Christian Faith and Higher Education Projects]: minutes, reports, proposals, 1965 Nov (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, reports, 1966 Mar-Apr (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Report to Project Committee from Christian Faith and Higher Education Institute, 1966 Oct (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee of National Committee
    - Minutes, 1964 May, 1965 Jun, 1966 May (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1966 Oct (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Addendum: Verlyn Barker Files, Series IX